honeyfund.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy at Honeyfund.com, the free honeymoon registry, the #1 cash wedding registry

_Last Updated October 23, 2017_

Thank you for your interest in Honeyfund.com, Inc. (referred to herein as "we" or "us") and our website, [www.honeyfund.com](http://www.honeyfund.com/) (the "Site"). This privacy policy was created to let you know why we collect information from you and what we do with it. By using the Site, you consent to the following terms.

This statement discloses the privacy practices of Honeyfund.com, Inc. It covers:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Honeyfund.com website 
  2. How the information is used
  3. With whom the information may be shared
  4. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information
  5. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

#### How we collect your information

### Information collected at registration

Honeyfund.com, Inc. collects personal information when you register with us and when you use Honeyfund services. Honeyfund.com, Inc. may combine this information about you with information we obtain from business partners or other third parties. During registration, we require members to give us basic contact information (such as your and your future spouse's first names, last names and e-mail addresses), wedding and honeymoon information (such as your wedding date and preferred honeymoon destination) and demographic information (such as your ZIP or postal code). Registration information is collected via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol (https). The information requested on the registration form may change from time to time. Although additional demographic information may be requested at the time of registration, only information marked "required" is necessary for registration and utilization of our services.

Users who register through Facebook agree to share their public Facebook profile, friend list and e-mail address via Facebook's App permissions interface.

Users who give gifts to Honeyfund.com members are not required to register. However, some information is collected during the "Give a Gift" process, including first and last name and e-mail address. This information is associated with the member's account. The e-mail address collected during the “Give a Gift” process is not shared with third parties. It is used by Honeyfund.com, Inc. and Site members to communicate with the gift giver regarding their gift. 

We do not accept registrations from persons under the age of 18. Honeyfund services are available only to persons who are 18 years of age and over. If we learn that a user is under the age of 18, we will terminate the account and delete the user's information. Honeyfund.com, Inc. will not be liable for any content or advertisements viewed by minor children in violation of the terms of this agreement.

### Information collected through use of Honeyfund.com

In addition to the questions you answer when you register for Honeyfund.com membership, we collect information necessary to create your honeymoon registry, including but not limited to at least one registry item and a contact person. Personal information is collected via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol (https). When you enter this information and publish your honeymoon registry, you agree to make it public and accessible by visitors to Honeyfund.com. Note you are responsible for obtaining permission to publish your contact person's information like name and telephone number.

Honeyfund.com, Inc. also collects system information such as IP addresses (in other words, the location of your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting, security, and to examine overall traffic trends. (For example, IP addresses help us determine the percentage of people coming from various search engines, such as Google or Yahoo!) This information, in aggregate form, is recorded for administrative purposes. IP addresses may be linked to personal account information for security purposes, for instance, to prevent spammers from abusing Honeyfund.com, Inc.'s e-mail features.

Honeyfund.com, Inc. and its partners use cookies, small data files stored on your computer, to customize portions of our site to your preferences and to analyze traffic trends on our site. For example, Honeyfund.com, Inc. uses a cookie to identify you as a Honeyfund.com member and to provide you with access to your personal account. This way, you don't have to login every time you come to the Honeyfund.com website. If you do not allow your browser to accept cookies, please understand that some of the areas or functionality within our site may be limited.

This Site uses Google Analytics. Aggregate information including but not limited to user traffic, site usage, demographics and interests is collected by a Google Analytics cookie and reported to us. You can opt-out of the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest on Google Analytics' [opt-outs page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "Google Analytics' Opt Outs"). 

You can browse the Honeyfund.com website without registering or providing any personal information. However, in order to take advantage of our honeymoon registry service, you are required to provide us with information such as your names, e-mail address, real-world address, wedding date, and roles in the wedding.

### What we do with the information we collect

Information we collect from your membership helps us to make your registry available to your guests, improve our content, customize certain pages for you, make third-party payment systems available to you, and provide you with promotional information and updates about Honeyfund.com, Inc. and it's affiliates.

### With whom do we share information

Honeyfund.com, Inc. does not share personally-identifiable information (PII) with third parties, except where reasonably necessary to provide you with site functionality including but not limited to third-party payment systems, to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. We may also disclose your personal information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our stock or assets in the line of business that this privacy policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization.

For more information about the sharing of non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) see "Advertisers and Honeyfund" below.

### Changing your personal information

You can access or update your personal information by logging in to your Honeyfund.com account and changing your profile. If you would like to deactivate your membership with Honeyfund.com, you should use the following Web page address <https://www.honeyfund.com/CloseAccount>. You may also contact Honeyfund.com, Inc. by e-mailing [help@honeyfund.com](https://www.honeyfund.com/ContactUs?s=Deactivate%20Membership) and writing "Deactivate Membership" in the subject line or write to Honeyfund.com, Inc. at 2605 Enterprise Rd E, Ste 320, Clearwater, FL 33759.

### Other websites

The Honeyfund.com website contains links to other websites. We cannot be responsible for their content or for private information that you may choose to share with them. Please note: Information you release directly to parties who provide services to Honeyfund.com, Inc., such as any vendors who advertise on the Honeyfund.com website, may be subject to different rules of use or disclosure. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing personal information to third parties.

### Disclaimer

Your privacy is very important to us, but due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. Under certain circumstances, the government or third parties may lawfully or unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we may disclose information about you to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

### Notice of changes

Honeyfund.com, Inc. reserves the right to change this privacy policy in its sole discretion, and will post any revisions on this Site. We encourage you to review this privacy policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. If there is a change in this privacy policy that affects your personally identifiable information, we will notify you of the change by e-mail to the address that you have provided to us. At the time of this message, you will be given the option to opt out of this change in information usage by sending a message to [help@honeyfund.com](https://www.honeyfund.com/ContactUs), provided, however that any subsequent use of the Site will subject you to the new privacy policy.

Honeyfund.com, Inc. encourages you to learn as much as you can about your privacy on the Internet. To find out more, visit [www.bbbonline.org](http://www.bbbonline.org/) or [www.TRUSTe.com](http://www.truste.com/).

### Advertisers and Honeyfund.com

We allow third-party advertising companies to collect certain non-PII information when you visit our Site, in order to serve advertisements for goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you on our Site and other websites. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-PII (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over). The use of this information by these third-party advertising companies will be subject to the privacy policies of such third parties, and not this privacy policy. These third parties may use information that they collect for online preference marketing purposes. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or if you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, you may either visit each ad network's website individually and opt out, or visit the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the [Networking Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of all network advertising cookies. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies.

### Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Honeyfund.com, Inc. by e-mailing [help@honeyfund.com](https://www.honeyfund.com/ContactUs?s=Privacy%20Policy) and writing "Privacy Policy" in the subject line. You may also write to Honeyfund.com, Inc. at 2605 Enterprise Rd E, Ste 320, Clearwater, FL 33759.
